{
    "subject": "resource/Simcere_Pharmaceutical",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Pharmaceutical_drug",
    "human_readable": "Simcere Pharmaceutical is in the industry of pharmaceutical drug.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9757502675056458,
            "question": "What industry is Simcere Pharmaceutical in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8837742209434509,
            "question": "What role does Simcere Pharmaceutical play in the pharmaceutical market?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8596057295799255,
            "question": "Are there different types of drugs that Simcere Pharmaceutical might produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8553736209869385,
            "question": "Could Simcere Pharmaceutical be involved in drug research and development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8370821475982666,
            "question": "Who are the customers of Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8010790944099426,
            "question": "What type of products does Simcere Pharmaceutical make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6921249628067017,
            "question": "Does Simcere Pharmaceutical operate in a global market?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6808468699455261,
            "question": "What is the primary function of Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5810545086860657,
            "question": "Does Simcere Pharmaceutical focus on developing healthcare solutions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5281362533569336,
            "question": "Could Simcere Pharmaceutical be involved in clinical trials?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Simcere Pharmaceutical is in the industry of pharmaceutical drug.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8098_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Simcere Pharmaceutical focus on developing healthcare solutions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8098_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary function of Simcere Pharmaceutical?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8098_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Simcere Pharmaceutical operate in a global market?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8098_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8098_53.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Simcere Pharmaceutical Group being involved in the development, manufacturing, and marketing of pharmaceutical drugs. This supports the statement that Simcere Pharmaceutical is in the industry of pharmaceutical drugs."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}